https://www.pmdcorp.com/privacy-policy?hsLang=en

Overview
Integrated Circuits (ICs)
Overview
Integrated Circuits (IC)
Performance Motion
Devices, Inc.
1 Technology Park Dr.
Last Modified: August 30, 2018
We at Performance Motion Devices, Inc. (PMD Corp.) are committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy applies to our website (Website), www.pmdcorp.com, which is owned and controlled by Performance Motion Devices, Inc. This Privacy Policy governs our data collection, processing and usage practices. It also describes your choices regarding use, access and correction of your personal information. By using the Website, you consent to the data practices described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with the data practices described in this Privacy Policy, you should not use the Website.
We periodically update this Privacy Policy. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy periodically.
Important Information
1.1. Changes to this Privacy Policy We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time by posting a new version online. You should check this page occasionally to review any changes. If we make any material changes, we will notify you by posting the revised Privacy Policy on our website. Your continued use of the Website and/or continued provision of Personal Information to us will be subject to the terms of the then-current Privacy Policy.
1.2. Contact Us If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our treatment of the information you provide us, please write to us by email at privacy@pmdcorp.com or by mail to Performance Motion Devices, Inc., 1 Technology Park Drive, Westford, MA 01886 USA, Attn: Privacy.
Information We Collect
2.1. When You Visit our Website You are free to explore the Website without providing any Personal Information about yourself. When you visit the Website or subscribe to our newsletter, we request that you provide Personal Information about yourself, and we collect Navigational Information.
We may link information we store within the analytics software. We do this to improve services we offer you and improve our marketing, analytics and site functionality.
2.1. "Personal Information" This refers to any information that you voluntarily submit to us and that identifies you personally, including contact information, such as your name, e-mail address, company name, address, phone number, and other information about yourself or your business. Personal Information can also include information about any transactions, both free and paid, that you enter into on the Website, and information about you that is available on the internet, such as from Facebook, LinkedIn, Twitter and Google, or publicly available information that we acquire from service providers.
2.2. "Navigational Information" This refers to information about your computer and your visits to this website such as your IP address, geographical location, browser type, referral source, length of visit and pages viewed. Please see the "Navigation Information" section below.
2.3. Payment Information For some marketing efforts, we may collect and process payment information from you, including credit cards numbers and billing information, using third party PCI-compliant service providers. Except for this, we do not collect Sensitive Information from you.
2.4. Information About Children The Website is not intended for or targeted at children under 13, and we do not knowingly or intentionally collect information about children under 13. If you believe that we have collected information about a child under 13, please contact us at privacy@pmdcorp.com, so that we may delete the information.
How We Use Information We Collect
3.1. Compliance with Our Privacy Policy We use the information we collect only in compliance with this Privacy Policy. Customers who subscribe to our Website blog are obligated through our agreements with them to comply with this Privacy Policy.
3.2. We Never Sell Personal Information We will never sell your Personal Information to any third party.
3.3. Use of Personal Information In addition to the uses identified elsewhere in this Privacy Policy, we may use your Personal Information to: (a) improve your browsing experience by personalizing the Website; (b) send information to you which we think may be of interest to you by post, email, or other means; (c) send you marketing communications relating to our business or the businesses of carefully-selected third parties which we think may be of interest to you, and (d) provide other companies with statistical information about our users -- but this information will not be used to identify any individual user. We may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, we do not transfer your unique Personal Information to the third party. In addition, we may share data with trusted partners to contact you based on your request to receive such communications, help us perform statistical analysis, or provide customer support. Such third parties are prohibited from using your Personal Information except for these purposes, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information. If you do not want us to share your personal information with these companies, contact us at privacy@pmdcorp.com.
3.4. Use of Navigational Information We use Navigational Information to operate and improve the Website. We may also use Navigational Information alone or in combination with Personal Information to provide you with personalized information about PMD Inc.
3.5. Customer Testimonials and Comments We post customer testimonials and comments on our Website, which may contain Personal Information. We obtain each customer's consent via email prior to posting the customer's name and testimonial.
3.6. Use of Credit Card Information If you give us credit card information, we use it solely to check your financial qualifications and collect payment from you. We use a PCI compliant third-party service provider to manage credit card processing. This service provider is not permitted to store, retain, or use the information you provide except for the sole purpose of credit card processing on our behalf.
3.7. Service Providers We employ other companies and people to provide services to visitors to our Website and our customers, and may need to share your information with them to provide information, products or services to you. Examples may include removing repetitive information from prospect lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments, supplementing the information you provide us in order to provide you with better service, and providing customer service. In all cases where we share your information with such agents, we explicitly require the agent to acknowledge and adhere to our privacy and customer data handling policies.
3.8. Security of your Personal Information We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your Personal Information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. We secure the Personal Information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When sensitive Personal Information (such as a credit card number and/or geo-location data) is collected on our Website and/or transmitted to other Website, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol. If you have any questions about the security of your Personal Information, you can contact us at privacy@pmdcorp.com.
3.9. Social Media Features Our Website includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button and Widgets, such as the Share This button or interactive mini-programs that run on our sites. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our sites, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Website. This Privacy Policy does not apply to these features.  Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy and other policies of the companies providing them.
3.10. External Website Our Website provides links to other websites. If you access those links, you will leave the Website. We do not control, and are not responsible for, the content or practices of these other websites. Our provision of such links does not constitute our endorsement of these other websites, their content, their owners, or their practices. This Privacy Policy does not apply to these other websites, which are subject to any privacy and other policies they may have.
3.11. Public Forums We may offer publicly accessible message boards, blogs, and community forums. Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose any information through our public message boards, blogs, or forums, this information may be collected and used by others. We will correct or delete any information you have posted on the Website if you so request, as described in "Opting Out and Unsubscribing" below.
3.12. Retention of Personal Information We retain Personal Information that you provide us as long as we consider it potentially useful in contacting you about our services, or as needed to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements, and then we securely delete the information. We will delete this information from the servers at an earlier date if you so request, as described in "Opting Out and Unsubscribing" below.
3.13. International Transfer of Information To facilitate our global operations, we may transfer and access Personal Information from around the world, including the United States. This Privacy Policy shall apply even if we transfer Personal Information to other countries.
3.14. Corporate Events If we (or our assets) are acquired by another company, whether by merger, acquisition, bankruptcy or otherwise, that company would receive all information gathered by PMD Inc. on the Website. In this event, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our website, of any change in ownership, uses of your Personal Information, and choices you may have regarding your Personal Information.
3.15. Compelled Disclosure We reserve the right to use or disclose your Personal Information if required by law or if we reasonably believe that use or disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or comply with a law, court order, or legal process.
Navigational Information
4.1. Cookies Performance Motion Devices, Inc. and its partners use cookies or similar technologies to analyze trends, administer the website, track users’ movements around the website, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.
We use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web server. Cookies are not used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you and can only be read by a Web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize pages on our Website, a cookie helps us to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. When you return to the same Website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the customized features.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the PMD Inc. Performance Motion Devices keeps track of the Website and pages you visit within PMD Inc., in order to determine what portion of the PMD Inc. Website is the most popular or most used. This data is used to deliver customized content and promotions within the PMD Inc. Website to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.
4.2. Log Files We may collect demographic information, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites using log files that are not associated with your name or other personal information. There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by us. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, internet service provider (ISP), the files viewed on our site (e.g., HTML pages, graphics, etc.), operating system, clickstream data, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used by PMD Inc. to provide general statistics regarding use of the PMD Inc. Website. For these purposes, we do link this automatically-collected data to Personal Information such as name, email address, address, and phone number.
4.3. Clear Gifs (Web Beacons/Web Bugs) We employ a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), that help us better manage the Website by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users.  In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user's computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages or in emails and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We use clear gifs in our HTML-based emails to let us know which emails have been opened by recipients.  This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns. We tie the information gathered by clear gifs in emails to our customers' Personal Information. If you would like to opt-out of these emails, please see "Opting Out and Unsubscribing".
4.4. Flash Cookies and Other Third Party Tracking Technologies The Adobe Flash Player (and similar applications) use technology to remember settings, preferences and usage similar to browser cookies but these are managed through a different interface than the one provided by your Web browser. This technology creates locally stored objects that are often referred to as "Flash cookies." PMD Inc. does not use Flash cookies. However, our customers of our software platform may create pages on the PMD Inc. platform that employ Adobe Flash cookies.  PMD Inc. does not have access or control over our customers' Flash cookies, but you may access your Flash management tools from Adobe's web site directly here.
The use of these technologies by our customers is not covered by our Privacy Policy.  We do not have control over third party cookies or trackers our customers use.
4.5. Advertising We partner with a third party ad network to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our ad network partner uses cookies and Web beacons to collect non-personal information about your activities on this and other Web sites to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests.  If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out by clicking here: http://preferences.truste.com/ (or if located in the European Union, by clicking here: http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/). Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising.  You will continue to receive generic ads.
4.6. Third Party Tracking Technologies The use of cookies and web beacons by any tracking utility company is not covered by our Privacy Policy.
Opting Out and Unsubscribing
5.1. Reviewing, Correcting and Removing Your Personal Information Upon request PMD Inc. will provide you with information about whether we hold any of your Personal Information. If you provide us with your Personal Information, you have the following rights with respect to that information:
> To review the user information that you have supplied to us > To request that we correct any errors, outdated information, or omissions in user information that you have supplied to us > To request that your user information not be used to contact you > To request that your user information be removed from any solicitation list that we use > To request that your user information be deleted from our records > To opt out of being solicited by PMD Inc. or third parties
To exercise any of these rights, please contact us at privacy@pmdcorp.com or by mail to Performance Motion Devices, Inc., 1 Technology Park Drive, Westford, MA 01886 USA, Attention: Privacy. We will respond to your request to change, correct, or delete your information within a reasonable timeframe and notify you of the action we have taken.
Should you request a copy of your Personal Information, we will supply the first copy will be provided free of charge, but additional copies may be subject to a reasonable fee. Should you request the deletion of your Personal Information, PMD Inc. will generally do so as soon as practicable, although your right to have your Personal Information deleted is subject to exceptions, such as, for example, compliance with a legal obligation or for the establishment, exercise or defense of legal claims.
Please be advised that if you are a resident of or are located in the European Economic Area (“EEA”), you may also have certain rights under the General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”). You have the right to complain to a supervisory authority if you believe your rights under the GDPR are not being respected. You may do so in the EU member state of your habitual residence, your place of work or the place of the alleged infringement.
5.3. To Unsubscribe From Our Communications You may unsubscribe from our marketing communications by clicking on the "unsubscribe" link located on the bottom of our e-mails, or by emaling us at privacy@pmdcorp.com, or by sending us postal mail to Performance Motion Devices, Inc., 1 Technology Park Drive, Westford, MA 01886 USA, Attention: Privacy. Customers cannot opt out of receiving transactional emails related to any account they have created with us.
5.4. To Unsubscribe from Our Customers' Communications Our customers are solely responsible for their own marketing emails and other communications; we cannot unsubscribe you from their communications. You can unsubscribe from our customers' marketing communications by clicking on the "unsubscribe" link located on the bottom of their emails, or by contacting them directly.
Changes to This Privacy Policy
We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, we advise you to review this page periodically for any changes. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. These changes are effective immediately after they are posted on this page.
If you have any questions or suggestions about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us.
SUBSCRIBE TODAY!
Subscribe to our popular newsletter, Motion Control News, to get the latest announcements, technical papers, and solution notes delivered right to your inbox.
Performance Motion Devices, Inc. 1 Technology Park Dr | Westford, MA 01886 | P: 978.266.1210 F: 978.266.1211 | info@pmdcorp.com | Privacy Policy
© 2020 Performance Motion Devices, Inc. All rights reserved. View our Privacy Policy.
